const questions = [
  {
    "question": "Monday",
    "answer": "lundi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Tuesday",
    "answer": "mardi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Wednesday",
    "answer": "mercredi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Thursday",
    "answer": "jeudi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Friday",
    "answer": "vendredi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturday",
    "answer": "samedi" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Sunday",
    "answer": "dimanche" 
  },
  {
    "question": "week",
    "answer": "la semaine" 
  },
  {
    "question": "month",
    "answer": "le mois" 
  },
  {
    "question": "year",
    "answer": "l'ann\u00E9e" 
  },
  {
    "question": "January",
    "answer": "janvier" 
  },
  {
    "question": "February",
    "answer": "f\u00E9vrier" 
  },
  {
    "question": "March",
    "answer": "mars" 
  },
  {
    "question": "April",
    "answer": "avril" 
  },
  {
    "question": "May",
    "answer": "mai" 
  },
  {
    "question": "June",
    "answer": "juin" 
  },
  {
    "question": "July",
    "answer": "julliet" 
  },
  {
    "question": "August",
    "answer": "ao\u00FBt" 
  },
  {
    "question": "September",
    "answer": "septembre" 
  },
  {
    "question": "October",
    "answer": "octobre" 
  },
  {
    "question": "November",
    "answer": "novembre" 
  },
  {
    "question": "December",
    "answer": "d\u00E9cembre" 
  },
  {
    "question": "the seasons",
    "answer": "les saisons" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Summer",
    "answer": "l'\u00E9t\u00E9" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Fall",
    "answer": "l'automne" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Winter",
    "answer": "l'hiver" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Spring",
    "answer": "le printemps" 
  },
  {
    "question": "directions",
    "answer": "les directions" 
  },
  {
    "question": "North",
    "answer": "le nord" 
  },
  {
    "question": "South",
    "answer": "le sud" 
  },
  {
    "question": "East",
    "answer": "l'est" 
  },
  {
    "question": "West",
    "answer": "l'ouest" 
  },
  {
    "question": "beach",
    "answer": "la plage" 
  },
  {
    "question": "lake",
    "answer": "le lac" 
  },
  {
    "question": "ocean",
    "answer": "l'oc\u00E9an" 
  },
  {
    "question": "pool",
    "answer": "la piscine" 
  },
  {
    "question": "sea",
    "answer": "la mer" 
  },
  {
    "question": "water",
    "answer": "l'eau" 
  },
  {
    "question": "river",
    "answer": "la rivi\u00E8re" 
  }
]